

Rishad Azizi Civil Engineer

Project Engineer

Sales Engineer

Purchasing Engineer

Telephone 90 555 0100512

Email rishadazizi@hotmail.com website www.rishadazizi.com

Address Istanbul, Tr

Profile

An enthusiastic and highly motivated individual who has a clear understanding of the role and responsibilities associated with being an engineer. Have gained lots of laboratorial and practical works in different countries (UK, Greece, Afghanistan, Turkey, Russia, Portugal, Cypress, Poland, Georgia, Ireland, France, Austria and Egypt) and have participated different company's programs (AFRUS, WYFEGYPT, AFTUR, GERYF, KOSGEB, TÜBİTAK, AFGTALENT, BİGUK, WFYS2017, UKINVENTS and THE YOUNG INVENTORS) for field and office experience. Have gained the experiences of Construction Internship. Office Internship, Laboratory Internship, Academic Project Research Work and Laboratory Work. Active developer and inventor of three R.D. projects and busy with ongoing researches at the lab of the KOU and R.D. company. I feel that my strongest strengths are firstly having a passion for Engineering career, Secondly an ability to understand and prioritize my study in a changing educational environment, thereby helping me to successfully deliver results.

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Pashto	Native	Native	Native
Dari (AFG)	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent
Persian(Iran)	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent
English	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent
Turkish	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent
Arabic	Excellent	Excellent	Good
Urdu (PAK)	V. Good	Good	V. Good
Hindi (IND)	V. Good	Good	V. Good
Uzbek	Good	Good	Poor
Portuguese	Good	Good	Poor
Spanish	Good	Good	Poor
Chinese	New starter- Reginner		

References; "It will be indicated if desired."

Educational Background

- Bachelor in Civil Engineering, UBI Portugal 2014-2017
- ✓ Bachelor Courses in Civil Engineering, Sakarya University-Turkey 2015-2016
- ✓ Bachelor Courses in Civil Engineering, Fırat University–Turkey 2016-2017
- ✓ Master in Geotechnical Engineering, Sakarya University Sakarya / Turkey 2017-2018
- ✓ Project Academic Researcher + Associate Professor Assistant, Dundee University- 2017-2018
- ✓ PHD/Beng M.Sc. in Civil Engineering, Koaceli University Kocaeli / Turkey 2018 – (Contineu)

Experience

- ✓ Trainee Civil Engineering & Lab. Technician at UBI Portugal -2014-2015
- ✓ Trainee Civil Engineering at Nurel Construction North Cypress -2015-2016
- ✓ Student Consultant at Engineering Faculty FU Turkey 2015-2017
- ✓ Associate Res. Civil Eng. at DU Scotland UK- 2017-2018
- ✓ Project And Ability Program Manager Londond, UK 2017-2018
- ✓ Sales Engineer, Sales planning and External marketing specialist
 in Istanbul Turkey, Warehouse Racking Systems 2018/12018/11
- Purchasing Executive+Project Engineer-Istanbul Turkey, Akemi Chemical Crystallize; 2018/11-contineu
- Participant (AFRUS2017 and AFRUS2019) Global youth program -Russia
- ✓ Participant WYF Egypt 2019
- ✓ Europe and Erasmus Project Background: Greece, Italy, Poland, Portugal -2012|Romania, Germany, Hungary, Portugal-2013|Spain, Albania, Georgia, Bulgaria, Cypres-2014|Germany, France, Italy, Romania-2015|Poland, Netherlands-2016|UK, Russia, Ireland, Spain, Slovakia-2017|UK, Bulgaria, Cypress-2018|Austria, Egypt, Suadi Arabia Russia-2019.|Georgia-April 2020|

Interests: Technology and Grouth, Business, Reading, Traveling, Foreign Languages, Community Involvement, Sports, Web Developing, Designing, Creating PHP Designs, Autocad Designs, Photography, Videography, 3D Animation, Web Designing, Walking.

Engineering Attributes: Knowledge and familiarity contract technical specifications, Micro drainage, Civils 3D, AutoCAD, IdeCAD STATIC, SAP2000, 3Ds Max, MAP GLOBAL, hydraulic systems and Commercial Estates, Design Guides for Highways in Residential, Geotechnical testing, structures engineering, XP Professional, all office programs and software programs.

Career Goals: My current, short-term goal is to develop and use my background education and communication skills. However, I eventually want to develop into a position that allows me to continue to use these skills while also managing a marketing group. I will prepare myself for this goal by taking on leadership position in team projects and developing my professional career by attending leadership conferences, activities and team Project works.